Best Hummus. 40 min · 8 servings · Middle Eastern
Ingredients: 12. 1 can (15 ounces) chickpeas, rinsed and drained, or 1 1/2 cups cooked chickpeas; 1/2 teaspoon baking soda (if using canned chickpeas); 1/4 c…
Step 1. Place the chickpeas in a medium saucepan and add the baking soda. Cover the chickpeas by several inches of water, then bring the mixture to a boil ov…
Step 2. Meanwhile, in a food processor or high-powered blender, combine the lemon juice, garlic, and salt. Process until the garlic is very finely chopped, t…
Step 3. Add the tahini to the food processor and blend until the mixture is thick and creamy, stopping to scrape down any tahini stuck to the sides and botto…
Step 4. While running the food processor, drizzle in 2 tablespoons ice water. Scrape down the food processor, and blend until the mixture is ultra smooth, pa…
Step 5. Add the cumin and the drained, over-cooked chickpeas to the food processor. While blending, drizzle in the olive oil. Blend until the mixture is supe…
Step 6. Taste, and adjust as necessary.
Step 7. Scrape the hummus into a serving bowl or platter, and use a spoon to create nice swooshes on top. Top with garnishes of your choice, and serve. Lefto…
You're ready. Use Make It for checkboxes on the page.